https://tate.com/privacy/

Search...
1-800-800-TATEContact UsOur Safety Rating
Get a Quote
Equipment
Equipment
BoilersServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersFiltrationServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersCompressorsServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersPumpsServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersHVACServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersElectricalServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersServiceEmergency ServiceEfficiency AuditsDesign & InstallationMonitoring & ControlsPreventative MaintenanceTrainingRentalsBoilersCompressorsAir ConditioningPower & GeneratorsIndustry SpecialitiesFood Processing PlantsData CentersCommercialHealthcareAbout UsLocationsCustomer ServiceCareersMechanical Insights
Equipment
Equipment
BoilersServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersFiltrationServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersCompressorsServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersPumpsServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersHVACServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersElectricalServicesPartsPreventative MaintenanceManufacturersServiceEmergency ServiceEfficiency AuditsDesign & InstallationMonitoring & ControlsPreventative MaintenanceTrainingRentalsBoilersCompressorsAir ConditioningPower & GeneratorsIndustry SpecialitiesFood Processing PlantsData CentersCommercialHealthcareAbout UsLocationsCustomer ServiceCareersMechanical InsightsServiceRentalsIndustry SpecialitiesAbout UsMechanical Insights
Get a Quote
Tate’s Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Tate Engineering uses and protects any information that you give Tate Engineering when you use this website.
Tate Engineering is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Tate Engineering may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 07/01/20.
What We Collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title.
Business/employer name and address.
Personal contact information including email address.
Demographic information such as interests or preferences.
Other information relevant to our industry or customers.
What We Do with the Information We Gather
We collect customer and website visitor information as a means to follow up with individuals who have shown interest or inquired through our website, to keep user information for vendors and clients that are registered through our file-sharing portal, to understand our user needs and provide users and clients with better service, and in particular, for the following reasons:
Internal records.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails to the email address which you have provided, regarding “Tate Engineering” products and services or other information which we think you may find interesting.
We may use the information to customize our website according to your interests.
We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.
We will never sell your information.
Security
Tate Engineering uses commercially reasonable physical, organizational and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information.
We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Tate Engineering and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets us know when you visit our site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Tracking Pixels
We also collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of tracking/website pixels. A tracking pixel is a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a web page or online advertisement and, in combination with a cookie, allows for the collection of information regarding the use of the web page that contains the tracking pixel. We use tracking pixels to tell when an advertisement has been clicked on or otherwise interacted with, and use that information to judge which advertisements are more appealing to users. We also use tracking pixels on our website to send digital ads to users who have visited the site. In some cases, we use third party service providers to help us collect and analyze this information.
Third Party Data
We also receive non-personally identifiable information regarding user demographics and preferences from users who choose to provide it to us from visiting the website, as well as from third parties who collect and make available such non-personally identifiable information for advertisement serving purposes.
Third Party Information Gathering
We may allow third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf and provide analytics services. These third parties may solicit personal information from you, and use cookies, tracking pixels and other technologies to collect information about your use of our website and other websites. This information may be used by Tate Engineering and third parties to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about each third party content provider, please refer to each third party advertiser’s privacy policy, http://www.advance.net/advancedigitalUserAgreementPP/.
Our Website May Contain Links to and From Other Websites
Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This policy applies solely to information collected by “Tate Engineering”.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
